jefit.com 2019-06-12

# Privacy Policy | JEFIT - Best Android and iPhone Workout, Exercise, Fitness, and Bodybuilding App | Best Workout Tracking Software

We use cookies to help make Jefit better. By visiting this site, you agree to our [cookie policy](https://www.jefit.com/privacy-policy). 

**JEFIT General Privacy Policy**

JEFIT provides an online service that allows our members to set up unique personal profiles and workout routines. In addition, users can share and exchange their own workout routines with other users. To enrich our users' experience, we request and display some personal information to other members and visitors. JEFIT users can change their profile information at any time and can control who can see their fitness results. JEFIT takes your privacy seriously. We are committed to ensuring that the personal information we gather from you is secure and confidential. We do not sell, rent or trade our customers' personal data. 

**Information Collected By JEFIT**

The information we collect in order to create your JEFIT.com account includes data such as your name and email address. The email address may be used to contact you with matters regarding JEFIT, such as a newsletter, notifications of new messages from other JEFIT members, or an announcement about a new product or service. We also collect some personal fitness information so that we can provide you with a personalized plan for successful weight loss. JEFIT also collects other profile data including but not limited to: personal interests, geographical location, gender, and age in order to assist our members find and communicate with each other. JEFIT collects personal information about you when you sign up for a JEFIT account. This information includes your age, metric preferences, and other personal fitness details. JEFIT also stores the data you enter about workouts, exercise, and anything you choose to track and keep records of. JEFIT also logs non-personally-identifiable information including IP address, profile information, aggregate user data, and browser type, from users and visitors to the site This data is used to manage the website, track usage and improve the website services. This non-personally-identifiable information may be shared with third-parties to provide more relevant services and advertisements to members. User IP addresses are recorded for security and monitoring purposes. 

**Cookies**

JEFIT uses cookies to store visitors' preferences and to record session information, for purposes including ensuring that visitors are not repeatedly offered the same advertisements and to customize newsletter, advertising, and Web page content based on browser type and user profile information. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site.You can configure your browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set. (Each browser is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences.) In addition to helping us analyze our web traffic patterns, JEFIT.com uses cookies to allow us to recognize you as a returning customer and to access your relevant information automatically. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. We do not place any personally identifiable information in your cookies. Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies. 

**Updating or Editing Information**

Users may modify or remove any of their personal information at any time by logging into their account and accessing features such as Edit Profile and Account Settings. Our JEFIT.com e-newsletter allows us to update you on new products, special offers and more. You can unsubscribe from the e-newsletter at any time by following the instructions at the bottom of the email. 

**Links to Other Sites**

JEFIT may contains links to sites. JEFIT.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. Users are suggested to read the privacy policy stated on that site.Our web sites may contain links to other, third party web sites. 

**Personal Information Security**

JEFIT makes sure that every online communication with our customers meets our high standards of privacy and security. JEFIT takes precautions to insure that member account information is kept private. We do this by using a secure server with software that encrypts all of your confidential information before you send it to us. We also protect your privacy by limiting employee access to and use of customers' personal data. In addition, we take a range of measures to protect all customer data against unlawful or unauthorized access and have in place appropriate physical, technical and organizational security procedures to protect against damage, loss, destruction, misuse and alteration of customer data. 

**Privacy Policy Change**

From time to time we may make changes to our privacy policy. If we alter our privacy policy in any way we will post those changes here. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal data, we will post those changes on our JEFIT.com web site. When you use the JEFIT.com sites to provide personally identifiable information, you consent to the collection and use of that information in accordance with this privacy policy. If you have any concerns, questions, regarding this policy, feel free to contact us at info@jefit.com.
